[
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1929",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/concatenation-of-array/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P001_Concatenation_of_array.java",
    "name": "Concatenation of array",
    "serialNum": 1,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-04-28",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Simulation"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1920",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/build-array-from-permutation/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P002_Build_array_from_permutation.java",
    "name": "Build array from permutation",
    "serialNum": 2,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-04-28",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Simulation"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1520",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-good-pairs/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P003_Number_of_good_pairs.java",
    "name": "Number of good pairs",
    "serialNum": 3,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-04-29",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Counting", "Hash Table", "Math"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1470",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/shuffle-the-array/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P004_Shuffle_the_array.java",
    "name": "Shuffle the array",
    "serialNum": 4,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-04-29",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2433",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-the-original-array-of-prefix-xor/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P005_Find_the_original_array_of_prefix_xor.java",
    "name": "Find the original array of prefix xor",
    "serialNum": 5,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-04-30",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Bit Manipulation"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1672",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/richest-customer-wealth/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P006_Richest_customer_wealth.java",
    "name": "Richest customer wealth",
    "serialNum": 6,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-04-30",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Matrix"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2798",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-employees-who-met-the-target/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P007_Number_of_employees_who_met_the_target.java",
    "name": "Number of employees who met the target",
    "serialNum": 7,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-01",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1431",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/kids-with-the-greatest-number-of-candies/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P008_Kids_with_the_greatest_number_of_candies.java",
    "name": "Kids with the greatest number of candies",
    "serialNum": 8,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-01",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2824",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/count-pairs-whose-sum-is-less-than-target/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P009_Count_pairs_whose_sum_is_less_than_target.java",
    "name": "Count pairs whose sum is less than target",
    "serialNum": 9,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-02",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search", "Sorting", "Two Pointers"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1480",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/running-sum-of-1d-array/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P010_Running_sum_of_1D_array.java",
    "name": "Running sum of 1D array",
    "serialNum": 10,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-02",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Prefix Sum"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2529",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-count-of-positive-integer-and-negative-integer/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P011_Maximum_count_of_positive_and_negative_integer.java",
    "name": "Maximum count of positive integer and negative integer",
    "serialNum": 11,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-17",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search", "Counting"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1295",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-numbers-with-even-number-of-digits/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P012_Find_numbers_with_even_number_of_digits.java",
    "name": "Find numbers with even number of digits",
    "serialNum": 12,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-17",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2373",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/largest-local-values-in-a-matrix/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P013_Largest_local_values_in_a_matrix.java",
    "name": "Largest local values in a matrix",
    "serialNum": 13,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-18",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Matrix"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1365",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/largest-local-values-in-a-matrix/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P014_How_many_numbers_are_smaller_than_the_current_number.java",
    "name": "How many numbers are smaller than the current number",
    "serialNum": 14,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-18",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Counting", "Hash Table", "Sorting"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2574",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/left-and-right-sum-differences/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P015_Left_and_right_sum_differences.java",
    "name": "Left and right sum differences",
    "serialNum": 15,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-19",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Prefix Sum"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-807",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/max-increase-to-keep-city-skyline/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P016_Max_increase_to_keep_city_skyline.java",
    "name": "Max increase to keep city skyline",
    "serialNum": 16,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-19",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Greedy", "Matrix"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1389",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/create-target-array-in-the-given-order/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P017_Create_target_array_in_given_order.java",
    "name": "Create target array in the given order",
    "serialNum": 17,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-20",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Simulation"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1769",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-number-of-operations-to-move-all-balls-to-each-box/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P018_Minimum_number_of_operations_to_move_all_balls_to_each_box.java",
    "name": "Minimum number of operations to move all balls to each box",
    "serialNum": 18,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-20",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "String"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1313",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/decompress-run-length-encoded-list/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P019_Decompress_run_length_encoded_list.java",
    "name": "Decompress run-length encoded list",
    "serialNum": 19,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-21",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2125",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-laser-beams-in-a-bank/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P020_Number_of_laser_beams_in_a_bank.java",
    "name": "Number of laser beams in a bank",
    "serialNum": 20,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-21",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Math", "Matrix", "String"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2535",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/difference-between-element-sum-and-digit-sum-of-an-array/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P021_Difference_between_element_sum_and_digit_sum_of_an_array.java",
    "name": "Difference between element sum and digit sum of an array",
    "serialNum": 21,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-06-26",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Math"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1409",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/queries-on-a-permutation-with-key/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P022_Queries_on_a_permutation_with_key.java",
    "name": "Queries on a permutation with key",
    "serialNum": 22,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-06-27",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Indexed Tree", "Simulation"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/two-sum/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P023_Two_sum.java",
    "name": "Two sum",
    "serialNum": 23,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-06-28",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Hash Table"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2367",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-arithmetic-triplets/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/array/leetcode/P024_Number_of_arithmetic_triplets.java",
    "name": "Number of arithmetic triplets",
    "serialNum": 24,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-06-29",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Enumeration", "Hash Table", "Two Pointers"]
  }
]